<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Buktab</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="rs">\u20A8</string>
    <string name="Rs">\u20B9</string>


    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="context_menu">Context menu</string>
    <string-array name="sem_array">
        <item>Sem</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="sem_super">
        <item>Sem</item>
        <item>st</item>
        <item>nd</item>
        <item>rd</item>
        <item>th</item>
        <item>th</item>
        <item>th</item>
        <item>th</item>
        <item>th</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="dept_array">
        <item>DEPT</item>
        <item>AUT</item>
        <item>BIO</item>
        <item>CHE</item>
        <item>CIV</item>
        <item>CSE</item>
        <item>ECE</item>
        <item>EEE</item>
        <item>IT</item>
        <item>MAR</item>
        <item>MEC</item>

    </string-array>

    <string name="desc_list_item_icon">Item Icon</string>


    <!-- Nav Drawer Menu Items -->
    <string-array name="nav_drawer_items">
        <item >Search</item>

        <item >Manage</item>
        <item >Post Ads</item>
<item>Manage Profile</item>
        <item >Logout</item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- Nav Drawer List Item Icons -->
    <!-- Keep them in order as the titles are in -->
    <array name="nav_drawer_icons">
        <item>@drawable/ic_search_black_24dp</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_drawer</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_add_black_24dp</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_person_black_24dp</item>
        <item>@drawable/logout</item>


    </array>

    <string name="aboutus">
        Buktab is an online market for buying and selling books with ease. We focus on making the experience smoother and time saving. Now
        all you have to do is post an ad from our vast database and fix your price, sit back and wait for somebody to come find you. Or just
        go and search for what it is you need, even made finer by filtering by location and contact them with one touch of a fingertip. No more running around looking for what you
        want or stashing up your old books and letting them rot. Now every book is an investment.
    </string>

    <string name="terms">
        Thsnk you for your interest in Buktab. By using Buktab, you agree to these terms. Please read them carefully. \n
    If you use Buktab, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and
    password and for restricting access to your phone, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities
    that occur under your account or password.\n
    Buktab reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel ads in its sole discretion.\n
    You may not use a false e-mail address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the location or other
    content. Buktab reserves the right (but not the obligation) to remove or edit such content.\n
    Buktab does not warrant that product descriptions or other content posted by users is accurate, complete, reliable, current,
    or error-free.\n
    When an item is offered for sale by one of our users, the price is provided by that user and any bargains must be handled with
    responsibility by said user.\n
    Buktab is not liable to any of the transactions.\n
    When you use Buktab, you grant certain permissions to use your device. You may find them at your settings.\n
    Software terms\n
    Use of Buktab Software. You may use Buktab Software solely for purposes of enabling you to use and enjoy the
    Services as provided by Buktab, and as permitted by the Conditions of Use, these Software Terms and any Service Terms.
    You may not incorporate any portion of the Buktab Software into your own programs or compile any portion of it in combination
    with your own programs, transfer it for use with another service, or sell, rent, lease, lend, loan, distribute or
    sub-license the Buktab Software or otherwise assign any rights to the Buktab Software in whole or in part. You may not
    use the Buktab Software for any illegal purpose. We may cease providing any Buktab Software and we may terminate your
    right to use any Buktab Software at any time. Your rights to use the Buktab Software will automatically terminate without
    notice from us if you fail to comply with any of these Software Terms, the Conditions of Use or any other Service Terms.
    Use of Third Party Services. When you use the Buktab Software, you may also be using the services of one or more third parties,
    such as a wireless carrier or a mobile platform provider. Your use of these third party services may be subject to the separate
    policies, terms of use, and fees of these third parties.
    No Reverse Engineering. You may not, and you will not encourage, assist or authorize any other person to copy, modify, reverse
    engineer, decompile or disassemble, or otherwise tamper with, the Buktab Software, whether in whole or in part, or create any
    derivative works from or of the Buktab Software.
    Updates. In order to keep the Buktab Software up-to-date, we may offer automatic or manual updates at any time and without
    notice to you.
    DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

    THE BUKTAB SERVICES AND ALL INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) AND OTHER SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR
    OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THE BUKTAB SERVICES ARE PROVIDED BY BUKTAB ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS,
    UNLESS OTHERWISE SPECIFIED IN WRITING. BUKTAB MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS
    TO THE OPERATION OF THE BUKTAB SERVICES, OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) OR OTHER
    SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THE BUKTAB SERVICES, UNLESS OTHERWISE SPECIFIED IN WRITING.
    YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE BUKTAB SERVICES IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK.\n
    BUKTAB WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF ANY BUKTAB SERVICE, OR FROM ANY INFORMATION,
    CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) OR OTHER SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH
    ANY BUKTAB SERVICE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, UNLESS
    OTHERWISE SPECIFIED IN WRITING.
    </string>
</resources>
